Let me tell you, Mr. He.
Don't think just because you gave me the map,
you are safe now.
Then what else do you want?
If that map can't be deciphered,
you won't have an easy time.
You still dare to threaten me now?
I am all alone now.
I'm not afraid of you anymore.
All alone?
Really?
Chibe.
Ni'er.
You...
What is going on here?
Do you really think you sent them away?
Speed up and catch up with them.
Get ahead of them.
Yes. Go.
I clearly switched it
and successfully lured you in. How is this possible?
As a Chinese saying goes,
the mantis stalks the cicada, unaware of the oriole behind.
Tomorrow, you two will act separately.
Ikebe,
go to this place.
Yes. Kiriyama,
you take a detour to this place.
Ni'er. Brother.
Don't resist.
Otherwise, both of them will die.
Mr. He,
don't play any more tricks.
You've already run out of options.
I gave you many chances to choose,
but you didn't cherish them.
Now,
your wife, daughter, and Shangguan Ying
are all in my hands.
Which one do you want me to kill first?
I didn't lie to you.
But what exactly is going on with that map?
There are three maps in total.
Huo Lang has the last one.
Only when these three maps are put together
will it be complete.
Are you telling the truth this time?
Yes.
I've told you everything.
Can you let them go now?
Go back and wait.
When I find the third treasure map,
I will release them immediately.
What?
Didn't understand me,
or do you want them dead?
Old fox.
He Xiaobian.
If I hadn't followed those Japanese today,
I never would have thought
that you were colluding with them
and killed our eldest brother.
He treated you like his own brother,
and you betrayed him.
You are worse than a beast.
Banjin, you can't kill me yet.
After I rescue Yinger and Xiaoni,
you can do whatever you want with me.
Yinger? Xiaoni?
Didn't you send them away?
You're trying to trick me again.
Banjin,
listen to me.
I had no other choice either.
Masao Tahara used Ni'er and her mother
to threaten me,
saying he'd kill them if I didn't cooperate.
I wanted to send them away.
I thought my plan was flawless,
but that old fox Tahara
still saw through it.
He captured them
and now they are locked in
Masao Tahara's house in Qinglong Stronghold.
One wrong step led to another.
I regret it so much.
Banjin,
I hate Masao Tahara more than you do.
I want to tear him into pieces.
I almost succeeded a few days ago,
but he still managed to escape in the end.
You?
I figured out his hideout,
and sent this information
to Huo Lang with a flying dagger.
Huo Lang led his men to wipe out his lair,
but Tahara escaped.
That's why he came to Qinglong Stronghold.
Banjin.
You know martial arts.
Go save Ying'er and Xiaoni.
Once you rescue them,
I'll accept any punishment you give me.
I will go save them myself.
Listen to me.
Wait until I rescue Ying'er and Xiaoni,
then I'll come back and settle the score with you.
Major.
If we let He Xiaobian know now
that his people are in Qinglong Stronghold,
I'm worried he might take some action.
After all, this is his territory.
You've seen how cunning this man is.
He always pushes his luck.
If we don't make him clearly understand
his own situation,
he won't reveal the secret of the third map.
It's a bit risky to do this.
That's why I had Chibe
make some arrangements outside.
If He Xiaobian comes,
he will do it secretly.
He wouldn't dare grab them openly.
He still doesn't dare let the rest of the stronghold
know our true identities.
Exactly.
That's the exact mindset I'm exploiting.
Major, sir.
Someone is approaching us.
So fast? How many?
Just one.
What?
We've been exposed.
Get Professor Takeshita
and bring Shangguan Ying and the others here.
Yes, sir.
Hurry up. Behave yourself.
Hurry up.
Move faster.
Bastard.
Go.
Chief Huo has been out for so long.
He should be back by now.
Chief Huo said he'd hunt some wild game for everyone
to have a good meal.
With the round trip,
it's hard to tell when he'll be back.
I think he just doesn't want to come back.
Miss Cai, you are absolutely right.
My second brother, that's just his personality.
He can't stay idle anywhere.
Right now,
he might be scrounging drinks on some mountain top.
What bad things are you saying behind my back? Second Brother!
No, no.
I'm exhausted.
Second Brother.
Where's the game?
What game?
I ran over half of Shanzhou.
My horse is exhausted.
I haven't even seen a shadow of this Tahara Masao.
No, Chief Huo.
You went looking for Tahara Masao
without telling us.
Do you know how dangerous that is?
What good would telling you do?
I'm willing to face the danger.
I'm telling you.
I went out specifically to find Tahara Masao today.
He's lucky he didn't run into me.
If he ran into me,
I'd tear him apart.
You only brought a few men.
What if you encountered the enemy?
What do you mean?
Boosting the Japanese's morale
and destroying mine?
Alright, stop talking.
Tahara Masao is definitely hiding.
Even if he's hiding,
there should be some trace.
The people we sent out
haven't brought back any news.
Second Brother, how about I go scout again?
Go scout.
I don't believe we can't find him.
Shitou, bring my horse.
Be quiet.
Major.
What's the situation?
Ikebe was killed.
Bastard.
He Xiaobian.
I will make you pay with your life.
What should we do?
Let's go. To He Xiaobian's house.
Go.
He Xiaobian,
I didn't expect you to be so dishonest.
You promised
you would cooperate with me well.
But you have broken your promise time and again.
Today you sent someone to kill me again.
How do you explain this?
I didn't.
Tahara Masao, you misunderstood. I...
My subordinate Ikebe
was killed by your men.
And you still deny it?
I didn't do it.
I really didn't do it.
That was Liu Banjin.
He just tried to kill me too.
Aren't you standing here perfectly fine
right in front of me?
How dare you lie to me!
These three women today
must all die here.
I didn't lie to you!
I have already told you all the secrets
of the treasure map.
I have no reason to lie to you anymore.
I really didn't lie to you.
I have no patience left for your nonsense.
Today I will make you understand
that you will pay for your cleverness.
Of the three women,
one must die.
You choose.
Tahara Masao,
you can't go back on your word!
Every word I said is true.
Don't kill them!
I beg you.
Let them go.
I don't believe your words anymore.
Of these three women,
one must die today.
You choose.
No.
I won't choose.
If you won't choose,
then I will.
You definitely can't bear to part with your wife.
And you definitely can't bear to part with your daughter.
Then there is only Miss Shangguan.
Shangguan Ying, you will take the fall for He Xiaobian.
Mother!
Meixiang!
This is what happens when you don't listen.
Take them all away!
Meixiang!
Major, there is a detached courtyard on the slope.
It is far from other houses.
There are only two people inside. Should we...
leave them alive?
Yes.
Go to sleep. Okay.
Who is it?
Can't you recognize my voice?
Go.
Miss!
Get in.
Mr. Tahara.
I am good at codebreaking,
not evading pursuit.
Not to mention coming for nothing,
I don't want to lose my life here.
Rest assured, Professor Takeshita.
Since I invited you here,
I will do my best to ensure your safety.
Now there is a clue to the treasure.
When I find the third treasure map,
we will be successful.
Are you sure this time?
It was exchanged for a life.
Besides,
I also have the two of them as bargaining chips.
I believe he won't lie to me.
Then as for the third map,
where do you plan to start, Mr. Tahara?
Don't worry, Professor Takeshita.
I will naturally find a way.
No.
If you want him to live,
answer my questions honestly.
Is there any other way out of Qinglong Stronghold?
There are, but they're all sealed.
You must have a way.
Take us down the mountain,
and I promise you two won't die.
Okay, okay, okay.
Meixiang.
My wife.
Darling.
With you gone,
what's the point of my living?
But don't worry.
I will definitely keep my promise.
I will take good care of Ni'er.
I will do everything I should do.
Otherwise,
after I die,
how could I have the face to be buried with you?
Meixiang,
wait for me.
Major, I only found this in the kitchen.
Major, why do we have to do this?
Now that we have these two people in our hands,
He Xiaobian will do whatever we tell him to do.
Kiriyama, use your brain.
Don't just think about killing.
Even though I killed He Xiaobian's wife,
and his daughter is in my hands,
do you really think
he will obediently follow my orders?
This man is not that simple.
Besides, in Qinglong Stronghold now,
even though he is the boss,
all the swordsmen here
are still loyal to Shangguan Bao.
If they find out
that He Xiaobian has joined us Japanese,
we will be like rats in a trap.
But then, why do we still need Qinglong Stronghold
and these swordsmen?
What's the use?
I never expected these swordsmen
to work for us.
As long as we ensure they don't cooperate with the KMT or the Communists.
Once we take Shanzhou,
I will deal with them.
I see.
Understood.
The third map in Huo Lang's hands,
we must get it as soon as possible.
Yes, sir.
Tahara, once we get the third treasure map,
we can quickly find the gold mine.
Then you will have made a great contribution.
Kiriyama, send a telegram to our superiors immediately
to request backup.
Yes, sir.
You, Baldy Zhang.
You fooled me and kept me from sleeping.
Just you wait.
See if I don't teach you a lesson, you brat.
Who is it?
Brother Banjin, you are not dead!
Good boy, you've become a patrol chief,
and now you dare to curse me.
I wouldn't dare.
Aren't I perfectly alive?
Brother Banjin, even if I'm a patrol chief,
it's not as good as when I was with you.
Besides, how could I curse you?
Isn't it what they say in the stronghold?
Then pretend you didn't see me.
Got it.
Let me ask you.
Did anything happen in the stronghold recently?
Things have been happening non-stop recently.
Boss He's wife
was killed yesterday.
They haven't found the killer yet.
Boss He was even tied up.
I untied him myself.
Boss He has given the word:
keep the gates closed.
Not even a fly can get out,
let alone outsiders.
They definitely can't get in.
I didn't rest all night yesterday.
I just got off my shift.
Then where are you going now?
It's Baldy Zhang who guards the gate.
I've waited a long time
and still haven't seen him.
I'm going to his house to check.
Normally he is very punctual,
but I still haven't seen him.
This is strange.
- Let's go. I'll go with you.
- Okay.
Lao Zhang.
Nobody make a sound.
Baldy Zhang.
Lao Zhang.
Lao Zhang, Lao Zhang.
Baldy Zhang.
Open the door! Open the door!
Lao Zhang, tell him you caught a cold
and can't go out.
Tell him to go back. What's going on?
Baldy Zhang.
I caught a cold and can't go out.
Where is your dad?
Tell your dad to come out.
Don't tell me your dad caught a cold too.
My dad also caught a cold.
We can't go out.
You should leave now,
or you'll get infected.
It's really strange.
Usually these two are as strong as an ox.
Today they both caught a cold.
Don't forget what I told you.
Okay, let's go.
I say, Baozi.
What is it that you couldn't say in the cave
and had to come out here to say?
Boss Huo.
This matter really has to be discussed out here.
It can't be anything shameful, right?
It's a secret.
A secret?
No one's around, tell me.
When Chief Shangguan Bao was alive,
he told me something.
The old Chief
discovered a gold mine.
He drew a map and hid it in three parts.
One part was given to Chief Shangguan Bao,
one to the Chief of Zhenshanliang,
and the last part is hidden with you.
No, it's with me?
Why didn't I know about it?
Don't be anxious, let me finish.
Go on.
In order to protect the treasure, the old Chief
carefully designed the hiding places.
Not to mention you,
even when the Chief of Zhenshanliang was alive,
he didn't know.
After he died, I retrieved that map
and gave it to Chief Shangguan Bao.
After the Chief passed away,
both maps fell into He Xiaobian's hands.
No.
What I'm most worried about now
is that the secret of the gold mine
has also fallen into the hands of the Japanese.
Do you mean
you want me to help you find the third treasure map?
I don't want you to help me find it.
I want you to keep it safe once you find it.
It must not fall into the hands of the Japanese.
This is the wealth of our Sandaoyuan.
We can never let outsiders plunder it.
I always thought the old Chief
favored Shangguan Bao.
I never thought
that the old Chief still cared about me.
Old Chief,
Huo Lang
has always missed you.
Chief Huo, don't be too sad.
Think about it,
when the old Chief was alive,
did he leave anything for you?
He didn't leave anything.
Yes,
he just gave me this scabbard.
I matched the sword later.
I've seen it.
There's nothing inside the scabbard.
The scabbard can be said to
curb Huo Lang's hostility.
It can also be said
that when necessary,
it curbs my dagger.
The secret lies in this scabbard.
Keep it safe.
Without this third map,
even if they have the first two,
it's useless.
Okay, I will definitely keep it safe.
Hurry, take the hostage away.
Yinger, go.
Yinger,
Uncle Liu is here to save you.
Uncle, it's fine.
Come here.
Go.
Keep an eye on them. I'll get some food.
Yes, sir.
Boss Huo.
What is it?
Boss, someone is outside the cave.
Who?
A big guy. Looks injured.
And he's carrying a little girl.
What's his name?
Said he's from Qinglong Stronghold.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
It's... It's Liu Banjin.
Mr. Liu.
Mr. Liu, it's you.
What happened, Xiaoni?
Xiaoni, come.
How did you get hurt?
It's nothing. Just a scratch.
Quick, help him inside.
Go.
Come, Xiaoni.
Let's treat the wound. Come.
You are as strong as an ox.
Who did this?
You got hurt.
The Japs.
It's right here.
This is a new liaison point set up by the Tokumu Kikan.
The shopkeeper is Chinese.
He's also our informant.
Good.
Shopkeeper.
Did you find the person I asked you to find?
Yes, I did.
The swordsman named Meng Shigui
lives on Xixia Street.
He often goes to a nearby tavern to drink.
The tavern doesn't just sell liquor,
it also sells mutton soup.
It's called Yingsifang Tavern.
Very good.
Give us two sets of clothes.
Okay, please follow me to the back hall.
That's how I saved Nizi.
This He Xiaobian actually colluded with the Japanese
and killed our eldest brother.
When he first came,
I thought there was something wrong with him.
He's usually as quiet as a mouse,
and doesn't say a word.
Now look,
he suddenly dropped a bomb,
and a Japanese one at that.
Second Brother, can we stop talking for now?
Say the word,
and I'll take my brothers to Qinglong Stronghold right now
to kill He Xiaobian. Let's go.
Don't panic.
Mr. Liu, where is Shangguan Ying?
I failed to save her.
She was taken away by the Japanese.
Mr. Liu.
Where was Ying taken?
I don't know.
I'm here this time
to ask Boss Huo for help.
We need to rescue Ying as soon as possible.
You came to the right person.
I will definitely save Ying'er.
We'll attack Qinglong Stronghold tomorrow.
Second Brother, I'll go prepare.
Shitou, Zhuzi.
Come back. What are you doing?
Have you ever thought about it?
The Japanese haven't attacked yet,
and we're already fighting among ourselves.
Do you think the Japanese
are conquering too slowly or what?
Also, when Chief Shangguan Bao was alive,
he did his best to maintain unity among the strongholds.
Now we're breaking it just like that.
Our infighting
will only benefit the Japanese.
No, this won't work, that won't work.
Then what will work?
We can't attack by force, but we can outsmart them.
Outsmart them?
Master Liu,
you have a plan, right?
This kid is quite sneaky.
It seems the secret I, Liu Banjin, kept for half my life
is finally useful today.
Boss, I'll tell you.
Actually, there are multiple secret passages in our Qinglong Stronghold.
Multiple secret passages?
Then let's go in through the secret passages,
find those Japanese devils,
and save Shangguan Ying.
Right.
That's good.
Wait, wait! You haven't paid yet.
What money? Food money? What for?
For the food and drinks!
Sir,
please don't make it hard on us workers.
You haven't paid for your meals several times,
and we had to cover it for you.
You must pay us this time.
Do you even know who I am?
I'm Mr. Meng!
Am I someone you can afford to mess with?
Call your boss over. No,
I'll beat him up too.
What Uncle Meng?
Beat him.
Not paying! You ate without paying!
I'll beat you to death! You ate without paying!
Beat you to death!
Stop, stop!
Boss, what's going on?
He ate without paying.
It's happened several times.
Boss, is this enough?
Is it enough?
Enough, enough, enough.
Go back.
The current situation is getting more and more severe.
The united front work has reached a deadlock again.
I must quickly figure out a way.
I can't just sit here and wait for death.
Our missions keep failing,
and the Japanese are becoming more rampant.
Now the boss has been murdered,
and Yinger was captured.
Don't be so depressed.
Who said all the missions failed?
We got the vaccines,
saved the civilians and the underground party,
and blew up the armory.
Aren't these all victories?
When two armies fight,
there are always wins and losses.
The most important thing is that we can't give up.
We are going to rescue Yinger tomorrow.
How sure are you about this?
I thought about it carefully.
She was taken by Masao Tahara,
only to be used as a hostage.
So her life shouldn't be in danger for now.
Right now, the most important thing
is to control He Xiaobian.
We can't let him collude with the Japanese,
otherwise Qinglong Stronghold will be lost.
We still need to think about saving Shangguan Ying.
This niece of mine
takes after her father, Second Brother.
Second Brother.
I don't know.
Second Brother. Second Brother.
Meng Shigui.
Go, go, go. Go and have a look.
Chief Huo.
This person is not trustworthy. We must be on guard.
Okay.
Brother.
Brother, I missed you so much.
Wait, where did you come from?
This...
Brother.
Meng Shigui.
When we were fighting the Japanese
in Luoyang City,
where were you?
Why didn't you think of Second Brother then?
Second Brother, you ran away
faster than anyone else.
Second Brother,
Wang Shi'er, I swear to God!
If I didn't run, I would have been killed.
Second Brother, look at my wound.
I see it.
Hurry up
and take him back.
It's just a small scratch, walk by yourself.
He can't go back.
Second Brother,
why?
Boss Huo,
I have reliable information
that Meng Shigui is a Japanese spy.
Don't believe him.
Second Brother.
No,
if he is a spy,
we need proof, don't we?
Where is the proof?
A spy? Where is the evidence?
Second Brother,
don't listen to him sow discord between us.
If anyone is a spy,
he is, Second Brother.
Second Brother, believe me.